The former Prime Minister, Mr. Wentworth Lane, was defeated in the recent elections.
He is now retiring from political life and has gone abroad.
My friend, Patrick, has always been a fanatical opponent of Mr. Lane's Radical Progressive Party.
After the elections, Patrick went to the former Prime Minister's house.
When he asked if Mr. Lane lived there, the policeman on duty told him that since his defeat, the ex -Prime Minister had gone abroad.
On the following day, Patrick went to the hou se again.
The same policeman was just walking slowly past the entrance, when Patrick asked the same question.
Though a little suspicious this time, the policeman gave him the same answer.
The day after, Patrick went to the house once more and asked exactly the same question.
This time, the policeman lost his temper.
'I told you yesterday and the day before yesterday,' he shouted, 'Mr. Lane was defeated in the elections.
He has retired from political life and gone to live abroad!"
'I know,' answered Patrick, 'but I love to hear you say it!'